The
next
is
a
song
that
is
a
song
.
I
would like
to
introduce myself
one
word
from
everyone
.
I'm
Nagomi
Saisho
.
Thank you.
Yes,
I was
looking forward to
seeing you
.
Thank you
for
coming
today.
I'll do my best
not to be
exposed
.
I'm
Chiharu
Hokaze
.
I'm
Chiharu
.
I'm
Ruri
.
I'm
Ruri
.
I'm
Ruri
.
I'm
Akane
.
I'm
Kaori
.
The
last
due
University
is
Three
second
speaker
Everyone
entered
the
elevator
.
However,
this
students
I'm
what
Yes
yes
Ky Nikara
this
song
Konnichi
go
to
that
near
between
will
I can't say anything.
But that's the first episode, so I want you to pay attention to their relationship.
I want you to pay attention to their relationship that you can't see on the YouTube channel.
I see.
How about the other members?
Well, I want to see Reika Sato's nickname when everyone meets her.
I'll do it myself.
I want you to see her nickname.
It's coming soon.
I'm looking forward to it.
I wonder what they'll say.
How about you?
I'm a maniac.
In the first episode, Miyu is working part-time.
I think it's already been released on PV.
There's a scene where she talks to the person who's on the way to work.
It's not on the PV yet.
Miyu is thrown the words that she said at the pre-recording.
Where's Miyu?
Why do you lose sight of me?
I wonder what kind of line it was.
It's a horizontal line.
That's pretty much...
It's not life, but it's a very decent thing.
I think it's very memorable.
The performers in the Afreco booth were also in a lot of trouble.
I hope you'll pay attention to that.
I see.
That's good.
Let's ask you something else.
How about you, Ms. Shiro?
This is the story of Akane Mariyama, who I play.
There's a scene where Akane writes in the first episode.
Actually, the characters are the characters that I, Akane Shirosawa, wrote.
Is that so?
Yes.
My characters are Akane's characters, so please pay attention to them.
That's good.
If you don't listen to that, you'll miss it.
But the characters are all the characters that we wrote.
Is that so?
Yes.
I see.
That's a good point.
Please pay attention to the characters.
How about you, Ms. Miyase?
I often have a quarrel with Ayaka Tachikawa, who I play.
There's a line that I say to that member when she's sitting in a chair.
Nanananana...
No, no, no.
You don't have to say that much.
You don't have to give me that much hints.
I'm really lost right now.
But...
I really like the line,
It's called,
Yay, I heard.
At the time of the recording,
the members told me that they were looking forward to the line.
I see.
I really enjoyed recording.
That's good.
How about you, Kawase?
Yes.
As you can see from the second PV,
the character I'm playing is called Black Nicole.
It's a strong-looking Nicole.
I'm surprised by the way she's acting.
I was surprised by her.
Especially for Miyu.
She's got some strong words.
And she's got a high pride.
And she's got a professionalism.
She's got everything.
Please pay attention to that.
I see.
Well, there's a relationship.
Yes.
How about you, Saijo?
Is there anything you can see?
Well...
Miyu Takigawa, who I play,
I think you've only seen her in the beginning.
But in the anime,
in the first or second episode,
I think you'll see a little strong Miyu in the next episode.
I hope you enjoy Miyu who you don't usually see.
I see.
I'm sure that's what you're worried about.
That's good.
There were many good scenes for the seven characters.
Yes.
It's seven times more fun to watch.
That's right.
This is wonderful.
Thank you.
Well, we've heard about the highlights.
Next, I'd like to talk about the song.
This time, the opening and ending will be in charge.
I think this is amazing.
How was the opening?
First of all, Saijo.
It's hard.
It's a song called Muzui.
I've already shown it at the live show.
It's a song that starts with my lines.
In the song, everyone says a line one by one.
What is it?
Personally, I think I heard Ruri Ruri, Umino Ruri-chan's lines.
I think it's Jun-chan.
I see.
Everyone has their own way of saying lines.
I think it's a good way to say it.
I want you to pay attention to it.
I see.
It's good.
It's a song plus.
I'm also interested in the lines.
There's also an ending.
Yes.
The ending theme is a song called Emerald in the sky.
When I listen to the lyrics, I'm really in conflict.
It's a very frustrating lyrics.
But when it comes to the chorus, it's a very refreshing song that's going to the future.
It's a TV anime.
I think the TV anime is 22 out of 7.
I think it's about the conflict between the girls who became idols.
I think it's a song that's very linked to that kind of content.
I see.
I hope you look forward to it.
Yes.
When each character is dug up in the anime.
It's called the Oto-Bankai among us.
Yes.
That's right.
Please dig your nose and teeth.
I wonder if that's how much each character is featured.
I was told to dig my nose and teeth.
Please dig your nose and teeth.
I'm digging my nose and teeth.
Dig your nose and teeth.
I actually dug my nose and teeth.
I dig my nose and teeth.
Well, you can say that you can tell what kind of character you are by digging your nose and teeth.
That's right.
What is it?
That's why I'm acting.
Fujima Sakura who I play plays the role of a kindergarten student.
I played the role of Sakura in the anime.
Sakura's voice is high.
When I play Sakura in the anime, I can't help but measure the age of the character.
If I raise the voice of Sakura higher than the current voice, it will sound like a mosquito.
I can't hear you.
Only teenagers who are watching this anime can enjoy the anime.
Please stop.
It's hard.
Let the old man say something.
I can't hear you.
Sakura is a kind and kind girl.
When I was a child, I was kind, but I didn't listen to my child's selfishness.
I tried to live with a little bit of words.
I see.
Next, I would like to hear from KAHASHI.
I said it earlier.
Nicole is very strong-minded, proud and professional.
What is Nicole's personality?
What happened?
What kind of encounter did Nicole have?
I'm really impressed with the reason.
I want to say it, but I can't.
I can only say this.
No, no.
I'm just happy to hear that.
I'm looking forward to it.
I agree.
Nicole's episode is very exciting.
I will do my best to act.
I hope you will pay attention to it.
I'm glad.
I'm glad to hear that this will be in the next episode.
Everyone is really emotional.
Really?
I cried while I was on a trip.
After the first episode, everyone clapped naturally.
That's amazing.
That's right.
I'm glad.
Do you have any thoughts, MIYASE?
I have a lot.
I'm sure you have a lot.
I will also act in my childhood.
Ayaka is in her early, middle and early childhood.
Wait a minute.
Let's change the age.
When was the prime?
When I was a child.
I played various Ayaka's time.
I think it's very characteristic.
I was able to grow up reading the script in my own way.
Certainly.
The leader is laughing all the time.
What is it?
Okaze-san.
I'm serious.
Listen to me.
MIYASE-san is talking about the prime.
I'm kidding.
I'll listen.
Then, I would like to ask you how you do the recording.
How about you, Umino-san?
Yes.
Since it's recording, there is a microphone work.
It's a microphone that can be used as a microphone.
I'm not good at it.
So, at the beginning, I didn't know which microphone to put in.
There are four microphones.
I was wondering which microphone to put in.
While everyone was talking, it moved like this.
It's like a half-spawn.
The sound is also noise.
Was it moving that much?
It moved a lot.
After the test, the director said,
Jun-chan, don't defend yourself.
Defense?
Soccer.
Sports defense.
It's a sports defense.
It's really moving.
It's moving.
Is it that difficult?
Who is the best at that microphone?
KAWASE-Uta-chan participated in the recording in the middle.
But she was able to put it in.
She is better than me.
KAWASE-san.
It's amazing.
What is it?
Nice to meet you.
What about you, KAWASE-san?
I think I have the talent for defense.
Is that your talent?
You're avoiding defense.
I'm avoiding it.
I'm afraid it's an offense.
When it came to KAWASE-san,
SAIJO-san was very obedient.
Are you good at it?
I'm good at it.
When I go to the other two, the staff is visible.
I only use these two.
Is that the intention?
Is there such a bond?
Was there such an intention?
So I don't know what they were doing there.
I don't know what they were doing.
I see.
You know about these two.
But it's interesting.
Maybe you have a personality.
Yes.
What about you, KOKAZ?
Well, other than the membership, I think.
I'm with other cast members.
I see.
That's right.
We have relatively little voice acting experience.
It's hard to say.
I can't say it many times.
I can't express my feelings.
I want everyone to do it at once.
I want everyone to step on my feet and say it.
Everyone tells me.
I'm experiencing that.
I think it's something that everyone does.
I feel like a TV anime.
I feel it on the spot.
But I'm happy.
You can absorb it on the spot.
That's right.
Thank you.
So, you're growing up in the one-by-one recording.
I think so.
That's right.
We say it ourselves.
I'm grateful.
You can learn a lot.
I can learn.
I can absorb it.
That's why.
Really?
Go to that party with me.
Next~!
I'm really happy.
Thank you.
To be honest,
you don't have to get off the stage.
If he goes to the venue,
watch the show.
I feel like my shoulders are lighter and easier to carry.
I'm always grateful for the words you give me.
So it's really a team play.
Yes.
Of course, you're a team member, but you're also working with other cast members.
Yes, we're really helped.
That's great.
How about you, Shirosawa-san? Do you have any stories about recording?
About recording? Well, I have a story about a new voice actor sitting near the door and taking a break.
I heard that's what it's like.
Yes, that's what I heard.
And since it's in everyone's heads, there's a group of members who sit near the door.
There is.
What do you mean?
You want to sit there?
I want to sit there.
You want to open the door?
I want to open it.
You want to be a door girl?
I want to be one.
Why?
Who's the newest?
I've been sitting there for a long time.
It's a little different from the time of the recording.
It's a little different.
It's like, I'm going to leave the door today.
I'll go somewhere else.
That's right.
I see.
So it's interesting.
You're building up your experience.
That's good.
So I've been listening to it like this.
Well, after all, the story of the anime.
I'd like to ask you one last time.
I'd like to ask you how you feel about this anime being broadcasted.
First of all, please, Mr. Amaki.
Yes, that's right.
After all, the anime's theme is the story of the beginning.
I'm going to tell you the story of their future activities.
I think 2020 is a new beginning for us.
For those of you who have been supporting us for three years since we were formed.
I hope that those who have been coming in from the middle of the calculation will continue to support us in 2020.
Thank you.
Now, let's ask another person.
How about Kawase?
Yes.
I'm new to the company.
I'm really excited every day.
I'm recording over and over.
Of course, Nicole.
Characters.
Everyone.
Really.
I'm a good girl.
Even if you look at it objectively, it's a really good anime.
I think it's a work that makes you think that it's really good.
From episode 1 to episode 12 and episode 13 of the extra episode.
I hope you can watch it without missing out on the first episode.
Thank you.
The more I hear this, the more I'm looking forward to it.
I'm saying.
I think I'm thinking about it myself.
Finally, here.
Can you say a word from Mr. Hokazu?
Yes.
Thank you very much for coming to the pre-show today.
No, I've talked about a lot of things.
Well, it's amazing.
With laughter.
With tears.
I'm really, really happy to be able to deliver it to you as a TV anime that was shot at the American set.
All 12 episodes.
And extra episode 13.
11 of them.
Please watch their story to the end.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
bör어
because
ha
Arira
Aje
Prue
Aww