The day of the trip
Good morning!
I'm Chiharu Okazuchi. I'm Ruri Ueno.
Today is the PR mission of the year.
We came to Hokkaido Sapporo.
We came!
I went skiing in Kushiro on a school trip to Hokkaido.
I couldn't go sightseeing at that time because it was Sapporo today.
It's not a sightseeing, but I came here today.
I ate a lot.
It's delicious.
I'm glad to be here.
I'm a grandmother.
My mother and father-in-law are both grandmothers in Hokkaido.
I came here last in April this year.
I come here often every year.
I'm glad to be here at my grandmother's place.
I want to promote a lot.
What?
It's black!
I thought the mission was a bit strange.
Is it a mission?
What is it?
The equipment Mie-chan gave me is a special one.
Let's go!
Let's take a picture of the current in the glass pyramid of Moere-numa Park.
Is that so?
Let's go this way.
Let's go to the Tapporo Kiboten Tower Record and make the PR event a success.
Please do this.
I want to make it happen.
PR mission
Let's go!
Have you been to Moere-numa Park?
No.
I may have heard of it for the first time.
It's not at all.
I always shoot for the single.
Everyone has a very pretty face.
Pretty face.
I feel like that.
It's a very natural image.
I see.
You look good.
You're cool.
If you have any special talents, please say so.
It's a talent.
You're cool.
Snow?
It's snowing.
It was snowing a lot.
It's snowing a lot.
We arrived at Moerenuma Park!
Look at this view!
Isn't it amazing?
Where should we take a picture?
Where is the glass pyramid?
I don't know where it is.
We are going to the glass pyramid.
What is that?
Isn't it that?
It's amazing!
It's big!
It's snowing!
It's so beautiful.
It's snowing.
We should take a picture here.
Wow!
We should take a picture of the mountain.
We want to use the mountain as a background.
We can use the pillar.
This?
Yes.
It's a produce.
It's not a produce, but it's normal.
We should build the bridge.
The bridge?
Inst烛
I'm sorry.
You're fast.
I'm still...
It's perfect.
I'm back.
I'm embarrassed.
Your face is in a good shape.
My eyes.
Your eyes are flowing.
How do you pose?
How do I pose?
I can put my feet down.
Put your feet down.
You said you wanted to go to your sister today.
Yes.
I'm going to take a picture with you.
Your sister.
You look like a last boss.
Look down.
That's good.
This is it.
I'm wearing a white bag.
I see.
If you haven't seen the anime so far, you should watch this.
The first mission is completed.
I did it.
It was fun.
It was fun, wasn't it?
I'm excited.
And there's another mission.
We're going to go to Tower Records in Sapporo.
We're going to go to the pivoting store.
We're going to succeed.
We'll get the attention of the audience.
Thank you for your cooperation.
We're going to the main store now.
We're going.
We're going to Sapporo.
We're going to the pivoting store.
That's right.
It's a black and white store.
We'll do our best.
Bye bye.
You have a lot of leading roles, right?
Yes.
I would like to do that.
I'd like to do that.
I look forward to watching the anime, starting in January.
It's me.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Thank you.
Thank you very much!
Meat!
I'm happy.
Milk!
Milk?
Hokkaido people came to see us.
Yes, they did.
Some of them said they've never been to Japan before.
I'm really happy to be able to come to various places like this.
I want to do a live show with everyone next time.
I agree.
We'll do our best!
So please look forward to our TV show!
Thank you for watching!