Here we go!
Fukuoka, Tokyo
This is a video of the ceremony for the ceremony.
Welcome!
Fukuoka!
I'm Reina Miya who plays the role of Yatako Uchikawa,
and I'm Kanai Shirosa who plays the role of Akane Maruyama.
Actually, I'm from Fukuoka
and I'm from Saga.
We're both from Kyushu.
So I'm really looking forward to today!
The mission has been completed.
The first one.
Let's make the PR event successful with HMV and Rooks Hakata.
I want to make it successful with the two of us.
The second one.
I want to make the PR event successful with Dazai Futen Mangu.
I'm so happy.
I heard that you were going to make the PR event.
I was expecting it.
I'm so happy.
I want to make the PR event successful and eat Ume-gai mochi.
I'll ask you to teach me many things.
I want to make the PR event successful with the anime.
I'll do my best in Fukuoka.
The third one.
I want to make the PR event successful with the two of us.
I made it.
Yay.
Thank you for your hard work.
We're on the spot.
We're going to have a talk event.
I want to talk about Kyushu.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes.
I'll go.
Thank you.
I came to Fukuoka today thanks to everyone.
I'm really happy.
I'm so happy to be in Kyushu.
I want to have another event here.
Please come to Fukuoka.
Thank you.
I'm back in Fukuoka.
Welcome back.
Thank you.
The event is over.
I had a talk with Kyushu, my favorite city.
It was fun.
I'm sure I want to come to Fukuoka.
I want to come to Fukuoka.
Thank you.
I arrived in Mangu.
Yay.
Thank you.
I used to go to Kourei-gi with my family every year.
I want to take Kanaeru, which I have never been to, to Fukuoka.
I want to take her there.
Okay.
What?
I want to go there.
Really?
Can I?
Yes.
Thank you.
It's warm.
It's fresh and fresh.
Thank you for the meal.
I'll enjoy having this.
It's good.
There are red beans in the rice cake.
The noodles are thin and have a nice texture.
It's delicious even when it's cold.
But, the warm rice cake is more delicious.
The rice cake is very chewy and delicious.
I want everyone to eat it when it's fresh.
It's delicious.
I'm not good at making Tsubuan, but I can make Ume-gan-muchi.
I see.
Everyone is lining up.
If you touch the rice cake, you can act better.
Where should I touch?
I want to make a good voice.
I want to say my favorite thing is my mouth.
Mouth.
It's a mouth organ, so I want to keep my mouth and throat healthy.
Wow!
It's difficult.
It's difficult!
I can remember it very well!
It's beautiful!
There are a lot of people.
When I was taking the exam, I got a 500 yen ticket.
It was expensive.
This one looks cute!
Ready, go!
Hope these soap operas open in Jan 2012 will be successful!
The story of Photoshop
Okay, we're done!
It's done!
Tada
The first episode of the TV anime will be a huge hit!
We've been doing the pre-recording for the first episode, and everyone is thinking about acting.
We're working hard with a lot of staff, so I hope it will be a big hit.
I hope everyone in Japan will watch it!
We've successfully completed the second mission!
I'm really happy to be with the members of the TV anime.
The omegai mochi was delicious, too.
I was happy.
I hope my wish will come true.
The Katabara is here!
It looks delicious.
I'll enjoy it.
I spent a day in Fukuoka.
I talked to Reinya about Fukuoka.
I feel relieved to hear the sound of the sound of the wind.
I feel better.
The TV anime will start in January 2020.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think it's an anime that will meet everyone's expectations.
Please look forward to it.
I hope everyone in Kyushu will see our growth.
Please watch the anime from January.
Thank you.