Osaka
Wow!
We came to Osaka!
I'm from Shiga prefecture, so Osaka is very close to me.
So, I came to this beautiful world with my friends.
I did a lot of fun things.
I've only been to Osaka by one hand.
I'm looking forward to today.
Really?
Yes, I am.
Let me say it.
I'm happy to be in the new world.
Thank you.
Mission card is here.
I'll open the first one.
Let's eat Kashi-katsu as a hit meal.
Yay!
Kashi-katsu!
I'm happy.
Next,
Let's watch the Tower Records' Osaka Maru Building 2 and make the PR event a success!
I did it!
I'm always in your care.
We are in your care.
I'm looking forward to the event.
I'll go now.
See you.
I'll eat a lot of Kashi-katsu to make it a hit.
I can't wait to see the view.
It's a good day.
We're going to win here.
I'm happy.
I won.
What's this?
I'm happy.
Two Kashi-katsu are in my side.
The one who can eat Kashi-katsu is the winner.
Really?
No way.
What game do you play?
I don't know but I can only eat one of these.
Oh!
Word Tying Sheet?
The answer is...
I see.
Group!
It's difficult.
You can't use these kinds of nouns.
But what about groups?
What about the other ones?
I want to play the game.
Group?
It's difficult.
It's Rii.
Rii?
Rii.
Please do Rewind properly.
You often do it, right?
Rewind.
If you do it in Kansai dialect, you will be in trouble.
I'll do it.
Rii. Rii.
Yanchamusume.
What?
Why is it wrong?
I think Jun Toda and Yancha are in charge of Yancha.
If you can do that, anything is possible.
What?
Yanchamusume.
Ne.
I see one.
I found one.
I found one, too.
What should you do in the order of makeup?
This is a group.
There is a group.
There are groups, right?
You can do it in order.
You can do it freely.
There are many of them.
What should I do?
Roo?
Roo is difficult.
Roo is really difficult.
Ruby is the only one that comes up in the chat.
That's true.
I don't want to name the members.
I feel sorry for you.
Ruru.
Let's keep the rules.
Yay.
I've never said that.
Kanae said something.
Which one?
I said, I'm not going to watch.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
Let's keep the rules.
Ruru.
Yay.
Let's do our best.
Miyako is close.
Right?
Yes.
I'm Na.
Na, Na, Na.
Nalala.
Na.
If I say it's wrong, it's not good.
I did it!
There are many people who say, if you say it wrong, it's not good.
There are people who say it's wrong, right?
There are many people who say, it's not good.
I'm the winner.
Kushi katsu is eaten by Osaka women.
I'm not a Shigayan.
It looks delicious.
I want to eat it.
It's a Japanese style kushi katsu.
It's amazing that you can eat Japanese style kushi katsu.
I'm very happy.
I'll eat the eggs that I like.
I'll eat it.
Do I have to take out the insert?
Insert is okay.
I'll take it out.
I'll eat it.
It's forbidden to put it on twice.
I put it on.
It looks delicious.
It made a good sound.
It's delicious.
It's crispy and the inside is soft.
The meat is delicious.
I'm sorry.
I'll eat the original taste.
I'll eat it.
I'm happy.
It's delicious without the sauce.
It's delicious.
The taste of meat is delicious.
I'm happy.
I wanted to win.
It was a hit anime.
I ate the original taste.
I'll buy my anime.
I couldn't eat it, but Mizuha ate it.
I'm full of power.
I'll go to Osaka Umeda Marubiruten.
I did it.
I'm happy.
I'm happy to see everyone.
I'm glad I can eat all of it.
I can't do this.
I'm happy.
You can do it.
I'm not tired.
I'm happy.
It's delicious.
I can't do this.
I'm happy.
Thank you very much!
Mission complete!
Yay!
Osaka is really...
People are kind and the food is delicious.
Even though it's a mission, we enjoyed it.
I thought it was okay.
Definitely, the anime is a success!
We enjoyed it and worked hard!
We will do our best to make the anime a hit!
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!