What is the mission for this year?
Tokyo
The last mission for this year is Tokyo!
We've been doing a lot of things together before, but we've changed the number of people in Tokyo.
Yeah, now we're having fun!
We're having so much fun!
Yeah, it's exciting!
Oh, I got it!
I got it for the first time!
Oh, that's right!
Ta-da!
Let's make a phone game that will make the heart and the members together!
What?
If it's us, then it's a game.
It's a phone game, right?
It's a game.
There's one more.
Here we go.
Ta-da!
Let's make the PR event at Tower Records Shibuya store a success!
Wow!
I want to do that.
Let's do our best together!
Let's do our best!
What's the point of success?
I don't know.
Let's do our best and succeed!
I want to do my best!
I'll go!
Let's go!
Wow!
It's a good one.
English!
Please say the following words in the pronunciation of the words written in the title.
I see.
I decided to be the last one.
Even if you make a mistake, you can do it.
Please do it.
The order of the order is a problem.
I agree.
I'm sure it's a good start.
This is the English professional, Sunny, who is the most popular.
I see.
Sunny is the first leader.
What should I do?
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
I'll be the first.
Please do it.
I often go with Nagomi, who is very popular.
She is Nagomi who is the second.
I used to study English.
She used to correct the movement in the middle when I made a mistake at the beginning.
Can you do it?
I have to fix it.
Will you fail here?
I don't know why I failed.
I don't know.
I'll teach you how to correct the movement.
I'll do my best.
Let's move.
I'll move.
I heard that everyone can't hear me.
Can't you hear me?
You are stupid.
You are too cute.
I think I can do it.
Listen carefully to Steve.
He is really caso shield.
What about here?
Filham coffee.
And slice carrot cake.
Please.
Please?
Yeah.
Go.
Is it perfect?
Yes.
I'll have medium coffee plus slice carrot cake, please.
I'll have medium coffee plus...
Slice carrot cake, please.
I did it.
I'll have medium coffee plus slice carrot cake, please.
I'll have coffee.
I'll have...
Medium coffee.
I'll have medium coffee.
Plus...
I'll have.
Okay.
Slice carrot...
I don't think I can do this one.
Cut the small carrots.
I think it's better to do this.
You mean, slice carrot cake.
Slice carrot, please.
Please.
Okay.
Is it possible?
Yes.
I'll have...
Medium coffee.
I'll have medium coffee.
Slice carrot.
Please.
I will have medium coffee.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I will have medium coffee.
And medium carrot.
Medium carrot.
Please carrot.
I'm not sure.
I heard you said please carrot.
I think I'm the first one.
I will have medium coffee.
Carrot please.
And carrot please.
Carrot.
Medium coffee and carrot.
And carrot.
Why is Sally the last one?
I don't trust carrots, so I'll buy them.
That's the answer.
Certainly.
Sally, please answer.
I will have medium coffee and carry out please.
I fixed grammar, but it's a little bit different.
I don't say carry out.
I see.
I say medium coffee and take out please.
But take out is to go.
The answer is.
I will have medium coffee and a slice of carrot cake please.
Slice.
Please.
Carrot.
Carrot cake has become a carrot.
Carrot cake hasn't come.
It's a mobile-correcting system.
Carrot.
I heard it when I heard it from the kitchen.
I heard it when I thought of a picture in my head.
At that time,
I thought it was a salad bar.
I see.
It's a salad bar.
It's fashionable.
Slice carrot.
I see.
Mission failed.
It's a one-time chance.
Is there any other chance?
It's a movie.
It's difficult.
!
A everyone who is not good at it
Doing research...
rebound
Drum andi
I'm going to play it.
I wonder if it's working.
It's cute.
I'm nervous.
What?
I see.
Can I play it?
I'm going to play it.
What should I do?
What?
How should I play the New Year's card?
It's good, isn't it?
I'm going to play it.
I'm going to play this.
Oh.
Would you rather play the picture well or play it more fun?
I am not sure.
I'm going to tap it.
But, understand it if this is here.
By the way.
Wait.
I might have changed.
What?
Holy crap.
states that
passe
'' lit up''
there are aX himself
'' I have a medicine. ''
what are they doing?
Wait, wait.
I got it!
Wait a minute.
What?
I got it!
Oh, yes, yes, yes!
I see, it's easy to guess.
But what should I do?
I got it wrong.
What else?
I don't need anything else.
I got it!
I can do it.
Really?
Yes.
I got it!
I think I got it.
Oh.
I got it!
Here it is.
What?
It's easy to guess, right?
I got it.
Wow!
I know it so well.
ETTEN
Wow!
I can type it so fast.
I got it!
I can do it!
This voice is almost blank.
Yes, I can say it all.
I did it!
Wow!
GO!
Go!
And I've completed it!
This image that you mentioned in your dream.
It's called ICHIFUJI.
NITAKA FAN NASUBI
What does that mean?
It means you can see it as your first dream.
So,
First Dream
Correct!
Yay!
I knew it!
It was a dream!
I want to see everyone's dream.
I'm glad.
Here is your first dream.
I see.
Next.
I thought it was New Year's Day.
I see.
But,
I wrote the date of the first, second, and third holidays.
Next.
I didn't know the information.
I only wrote this part.
You picked up the information properly.
You traced it.
I was glad it wasn't here.
I saw it and wrote it.
You are a good writer.
Next.
I wrote the date of the first, second, and third holidays.
You drew it in the calculator.
I made a mistake in the equation.
But, I am a commoner.
I understood it at first glance.
I was surprised.
I thought you were a bug.
I am surprised.
We completed the mission.
You did a great job.
I'm so happy.
Now that we've made you feel better,
I'm sure the PR event at the Tower Records Shibuya will succeed.
We'll do our best.
Last!
Please take care of the poster.
Thank you.
Please take care of it.
Now, we have 22 out of 7 members.
Hello, everyone.
We are 22 out of 7.
The anime is about the story of the beginning.
The story of the beginning is about the beginning of the story.
The relationship between the characters is...
It's hard to see.
It starts from the beginning.
Who did you get along with?
That's right.
Is that so?
What kind of relationship was it at first?
I was excited to hear that.
The difference in the way of calling.
The way of calling?
That's right.
And...
This girl and this girl are having a lot of fights.
That's right.
You can see a lot of different relationships.
On January 11th, the first broadcast will be on Toki Mx and BS11.
And...
It's a song.
I hope you can watch it.
Please take care of it.
Thank you.
I hope the anime hits.
That's all.
It was 22 out of 7.
Thank you.
So, this year's PR mission.
The last event in Tokyo has ended.
Yay!
Wow.
There were a lot of people.
It was a lot.
There were so many people.
That's right.
We were able to talk to everyone.
I think we made a lot of TV anime hits.
I hope the TV anime hits.
I hope so.
Yes.
Thank you.