Episode 1
The First Day of the
First Day of the
Um...
Onee-chan?
Hm?
Did you change?
Hmm...
You look pretty good in it.
Why are you dressed like this?
Oh, are you dissatisfied?
It's embarrassing!
I see.
You're embarrassed.
Then, when you wear a God Board for the rest of your life,
you can dress more embarrassed.
No, no!
I don't want to be naked every time I wear a God Board!
Then, you can go home without underwear every time you wear a God Board.
Or you can dress like a high school girl here.
Hmm...
Listen.
This is not a game.
You can't be naked.
You have to change your underwear every time.
You can't wear a God Board.
You're quite a service spirit.
No, it's a personal problem.
I'm saying that I'll get rid of your complexes and lend you my power to become a god of great love.
Do you understand?
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
If you do as I say, you'll be able to wear a God Board.
Then, before you learn how to wear a God Board,
you'll have to remember how to do the lesson.
First, read this.
The Theorist Boy
I...I...I'm...
I'm not the Holy Monk...
I can't hear you.
Too bad.
Read it again from the beginning.
But it's embarrassing to say sex in front of people!
What is the god of love saying?
Oh, well, it can't be helped.
Why do I have to dress like this?
You still have shame.
If you dress like this from the beginning, you won't be embarrassed to read the text.
Now, read it from the beginning.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
The Poet Boy, Take 2
The Holy War.
It's a famous Holy War in TV commercials, but it's not a story about anyone.
It's not just in the city, but also in the countryside.
However, the number of sexually transmitted diseases continues to increase.
I'm a virgin, so I don't have to transfer it.
Even if I think that there is no such thing as a woman,
I may get infected.
Continue.
Even though I'm not having sex with a sexually transmitted disease,
I may get infected.
In such a case, I got infected without knowing it.
If I transfer it to her,
I can't get rid of it without knowing it.
For example, in the case of herpes,
I may get infected just by going to the bathroom like an infected person.
Sometimes I get infected just by using the infected towel.
In other words, I don't know where to get infected.
If we really think about each other,
it's better to do the test at the health center or the hospital together.
Hey, sister.
Hey, hey.
What?
What kind of test do you do at the hospital?
In the case of humans, blood tests are common.
We do a blood test with a syringe.
Why don't you try it once?
What?
Are we also infected?
It's no exception that we are the gods of love.
But the way of testing is a little different from humans.
How about you try it?
I'm afraid of the syringe.
It's okay.
In the case of the gods, syringes are not necessary.
Rather, it's a little fun.
Then I want to try it.
I see.
Then I'll test you.
Chamo-namma
Toppuki
Namamakko
Chiku
Jashiyan
Chikuchan
Kouta
I'm glad there's no abnormality.
Hey, I wonder if I'm in a weird body.
It's okay.
It's not the level that affects your health immediately.
What?
Read the next.
The next reading is...
To prevent her from being infected with the virus,
Of course,
Let's put on condoms considering the cause.
There is an infection risk even in oral sex,
So if you use a vacuum cleaner, you need to be careful.
Also, the blood loss can lead to a sexual disease.
Let's make the genitals and the surrounding areas clean enough.
Then I have to tell you how to wash the genitals.
What?
It's okay.
I can wash the genitals myself.
You're going to do something weird again, aren't you?
Oh, when did I do something weird to you?
I'm a part of the class to overcome your complexes.
Even if I touch you.
I didn't do anything weird.
Well, I'm sorry.
It's okay. Don't worry.
Spinning toe hold,
I don't do anything weird.
I'm not going to do anything weird.
Don't give up.
I'm a female.