I'm a god!
Hmph, that's not a good ending.
Okay, let's go with this.
Nii-chan, what are you doing?
I've decided on my next job.
I was practicing introducing myself.
Oh, that's great! That's unfair! I'm jealous!
I want to go with you!
No, you can't take a criminal like yourself.
I want to be of help to you, too!
Please, I beg you!
If you really want to follow me,
then I'll take this as a no.
Reader Brothers
Episode 1
The
Nii-chan, I'm embarrassed.
Yeah, you look good.
Hey, why do you have to dress like this?
Listen, little brother.
You can't talk to a girl you like because you're nervous.
So, you can dress like a girl and make her get used to you.
You can relieve your stress and even get a mask.
It's a godly idea.
Hmph.
So, next, I'll wear nurse clothes.
I can't throw away my school swimsuit.
And my office lady and police mask.
Are you a pervert?
Huh?
Brother?
The Nii-chan, you're a pervert, aren't you?
Silence
Silence.
There are many people who say they're afraid of silence in conversation.
But conversations are not about talking to each other forever.
Sometimes, there are times when we fall into silence.
The problem is that the person in conversation will be convinced that the person in question is anxious about that silence.
Is that what you just said?
I'm not sure.
In order to teach people about the 1st, you have to know about the 10th.
I just showed you the example.
What's with that mouth?