If you love me, please don't go anywhere alone.
Please take me with you whenever you go.
Yes, I promise.
I will forgive you, King Ahaya.
I want to tell you that I love you.
Even if I were to be new to you,
I would like to express how much I love you.
When I see you,
Episode 1
The End
Hahaha...
Even so, I'm glad I succeeded in my diet.
Wow...
Who do you think is to blame?
Hahaha...
I'm sorry.
But, I was surprised that
you were so cute.
Hahaha...
I won't take it anymore.
Haha...
How cute you are, Ando-san.
Ando-san and I,
today, finally, finally...
Ahhhh!
Congratulations!
Shoo!
What should I do?
It's a stay-over trip, so that's what it is.
After all...
Ahhhh!
It's just the right time!
Shoo!
Hahaha...
By the way, today's stay-over
has a private bath.
Is that so?
I'm going in with you.
What?
Mokuto Chinken, the Sixth Stand
Funky Smell
What?
What are you talking about?
Hmm...
Ah, Ando-san?
Your comrade is...
I'll protect him!
Mokuto Chinken, the Sixth Stand Funky Smell
Why are you here?
Hmph! Adios!
Ah, Ando-san!
Damn it! I won't let you do that!
Rika-san!
Kaopa!
I'll play with you!
I'm the Comrade of the Land!
What's that?
I'll take you down with me!
Yeah!
Cherry Stream Attack!
How fast!
I'll get you!
You...
You guys are...
I don't know, but you look like you're a good guy.
You don't know, but you look like you're a good guy.
See? I chased you!
We have to hurry up or we'll be late!
Th-thank you...
Hey, wait!
What did you say?
We're meat-eating,
so we're not limited in age, but...
And we're wearing hats!
Ando-san...
Damn it! Where are you?
Stop!
Huh?
I'll have you die here!
Stop!
What's the official name of the Asadachi?
Eh? Asadachi?
Um...
Seppa! The Night-time Ghostly Pop-up!
Ah!
Eh? Ah!
Wait, could it be...
H-Hoshi-kun! And...
Spanking Wada-san?
Come on, hurry up!
Hurry up and go!
Thank you very much!
What is the G-Spot G?
Seppa!
Bremen Melt!
You're good...